

MAXIM JIMENEZ LAMAS

ASP Developer

About Me

Im a 20 year old developer, i love what i do, and i've been doing it for almost 4 years, ever since i was in high school i've been passionate about it, i'm currently studying at TecMilenio and look forward to new experiences

- •
- 729 158 4992
- Ninesdarwin04@outlook.com
- 0

5215, Av Estado de Mexico, Metepec, Mexico

Language

- English (Native)
- German (Basic)
- Polish (Basic)

Expertise

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Critical Thinking
- Fast learner
- Logical thinking

Experience

ASP Developer at Epic Games (Unreal Engine 5) July 2021 - May 2023

I worked with UE5 using the blueprint system and C++, i was in charge of blueprints and scripts for level sequences.

Game developer at Kyon Soft 2019 - Actuality

Currently working on a game using a modified version of Unreal Engine 5, i currently work on upgrading a custom shader (Kyon ARS) to make it look better and be modular for every single project in the works.

Education

Tecmilenio University

Bachelor at computer science (Software development) 2022- Actuality

Skills Summary

C# C++ Java Python Swift Prototype

Microsoft Office Unreal Engine 5 Unity

Data management Mongo DB Docker

Postgres

Mobility

Can travel.

I don't have a vehicle of my own.

What job am i looking for?

Full stack Backend Frontend